advanceautoparts.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy - Advance Auto Parts

At Advance Auto Parts, Inc. one of our primary – and most important – goals is to work to maintain and seek to ensure the security of our customer data. We understand that you may have concerns regarding the privacy of personally identifiable information. This is why we have specifically created this section; to address your concerns and answer questions you may have.

This Customer Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for Advance Auto Parts retail stores (the "Stores"), Advance Auto Parts Customer Care centers (the "Call Centers"), [www.AdvanceAutoParts.com](http://www.advanceautoparts.com/), [www.advancecommercial.com](http://www.advancecommercial.com/), [pro.advancecommercial.com](http://www.pro.advancecommercial.com/), [http://www.motologic.com](http://www.motologic.com/), [http://www.carquest.com](http://www.carquest.com/), [http://www.motoshop.com](http://www.motoshop.com/),, [www.autopartinternationalcom](http://www.autopartinternationalcom/), [http://openweb.autopartintl.com](http://openweb.autopartintl.com/) and other affiliated company websites (the "Sites"), our platform all other locations, occasions, or events where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of our family of companies.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or our practices, please contact us at 1-877-ADVANCE. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

## Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

As part of your interaction with Advance Auto Parts or the Advance Auto Parts family of companies, we may collect personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, billing address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information.

## When We Collect Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect personal information from you when you:

  * Create an account on our Site
  * Purchase, return, or exchange items in our Stores, through our Call Centers, or on one of our Sites
  * Contact one of our Call Centers
  * Utilize one of our in-store services, such as Tool Rental or Oil Recycling
  * Subscribe to one of our newsletters or emails
  * Respond to a survey or fill out a form
  * Register for a product warranty
  * Sign up for a loyalty program
  * Enter into a contest or sweepstakes
  * Provide us with reviews, questions, answers, comments, feedback, or suggestions

## How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

The personal information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways:

  * To enhance your experience

This information helps us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience in our Stores, through our Call Centers, and on our Sites. We use your personal information to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers, to improve the content of our Sites for you, and to improve your Store and Call Center experience.

  * To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us when creating an account on our Sites, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username. We will also communicate with you to respond to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

  * To process transactions

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use your information to contact you.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature

From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address and telephone number), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Site traffic or personalize the Site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), or to send participants an email related to the contest, promotion or survey (such as reminder or thank you notices).

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; such companies are contractually restricted from using our customers' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

  * To send communications

We may send you mail, email or call you with information about our product and service offerings if you have provided us with your name and address, email address or phone numbers at our Stores, Call Centers, or Sites.

If you place an order on our Sites, the email address you provide will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to Speed Perks or our promotional email list, you will receive emails that may include company news, program information, offers, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future promotional emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email. Please reference the Opt-Out section below. As always, you may also contact us via phone, email, or regular mail.

  * To send service-related announcements

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, please notify us by email, phone or regular mail.

  * To Email a Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Sites, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. Advance Auto Parts does not store your friend's name or email address in our database.

## Opting out of Communication

If you would like to opt-out of communication from Advance Auto Parts, we will ask you to select from several different options. Please note: order confirmation communications, Speed Perks Reward and reminder communications are considered transactional messages. Further, you may choose to maintain promotional messages from different programs or channels.

If you prefer to opt out of any of the marketing messages above, you may contact Customer Care, by telephone, by postal mail or by clicking the Contact Us link at the bottom of this page.

## Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on our member information page, your Speed Perks profile page, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail by clicking the Contact Us link at the bottom of this page. We will respond to your request to access within a reasonable timeframe.

## Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as our customer's name. Customer must consent to such use prior to posting. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@advance-auto.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Social Media

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs, reviews, ratings and other types of interactive social media. Please be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our social media sites contact us at social@advance-auto.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

In general, we may combine personally identifiable information about you with non-personal and other information including demographic information collected through our Stores, Sites, and/or third party sources in order to improve the customer experience including the uses listed above.

## Security - How We Undertake to Protect Information

At Advance Auto Parts we leverage technology and sound business practices in an effort to maintain the security of our customer information and we proactively look for ways to improve our processes. Additionally, we have internal training and awareness programs all undertaken in a further effort to help to ensure that our staff remains vigilant in their efforts to protect the information.

Among the technology solutions we use in order to help protect your information, is a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information and login credentials are transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider's database. Through this methodology, we seek to ensure that information is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems. Authorized individuals are required to keep the information confidential. Protecting your information is a business priority for us and we work hard to earn your continuing trust.

Regretfully, no form of electronic communication can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and so we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Under no circumstances does Advance Auto Parts or its affiliates or subsidiaries accept or assume liability for any damages whatsoever associated with the personally identifiable information.

## How We Share Your Personally Identifiable Information Outside Advance Auto Parts and the Advance Family of Companies

We share personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

We may share your personally identifiable information with other members of the Advance Auto Parts family of companies and also with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, collections processing, promotional services, operations assistance, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and our product reviews, etc. These third party service providers We provide these third party service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services and they are contractually restricted from using the personally identifying information in any manner other than in helping us to provide you with our products and services.

We may disclose personally identifying information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, advise you of a product recall, or otherwise to help protect you or us from fraud, scams, Internet security issues including phishing-type attacks or theft where required or permitted by applicable law. We will also disclose personally identifiable information when required by law.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities that we believe trustworthy. These are known as our marketing partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including some personally identifiable information about you, to enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. We only share the information we believe is appropriate to enable the marketing partners to carry out their responsibilities under our contracts.

We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information about our user base with the Advance Auto Parts family of companies and our marketing partners for research, website analytics and industry reports. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information

In addition to the information above, we also may collect data on customer shopping patterns while on our Sites. This may include how frequently our Sites are visited, the length of those visits, and the types of items our customers are looking for and whether or not a purchase is made. This information is collected to help improve the current and future shopping experience of you, our customer.

## Your Right Not To Have Personally Identifiable Information Shared

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. You have the choice to be excluded from our offers and promotions and to be excluded from sharing personally identifiable information with our marketing partners and/or our service providers. If you choose not to receive information from us, please reference the Opt-Out section above. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, phone number, and specifically what information you do not want to receive, such as "no phone offers", "no mail offers", "no email offers", or "no sharing of information with partners". DO NOT include your Social Security number or account number in the email.

We will respond to reasonable requests within 10 days, but please note that sometimes these requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to be effective, particularly if we are removing your name from postal mailings as these can have a long lead time. Even if you have opted not to receive marketing communications from us, when you purchase from us in our Stores, through our Call Centers, or on our Sites, we may need to contact you via phone, email, or mail, to address questions specific to your order.

## California Privacy Rights

This Privacy Policy describes how we share personally identifiable information for marketing purposes. Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, Advance Auto Parts provides its California customers the ability to exercise "opt out" rights as follows:

You may exercise your "opt out" rights, at no charge, by calling us at [1-877-ADVANCE (238-2623)](tel:1-877-238-2623).

## Third Party Links

Within our Site you may find links to websites of our partners, vendors, or advertisers. It is important to note that Advance Auto Parts does not endorse or have any control over the security of these websites. These websites have independent security policies, privacy policies, technology and security practices that govern them. We do not have control over their content or their security and do not accept liability of any form for the manner in which they protect and/or handle your information. We recommend that all consumers comprehensively review the privacy policy of each website that they visit to help keep them informed on how their personal information is treated and used.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are not controlled by us but, instead, are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Cookies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Advance Auto Parts and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics / service providers (provides online customer support and data to improve the online customer shopping experience). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the sites, tracking users' movements, receiving reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), for targeted messaging, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

## Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partners uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track users' use of and movements around the Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

## Product Reviews and Question & Answer Areas

If you use a Product Review or Question & Answer area on our Sites, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these areas. To request removal of your personal information from this area contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Email Privacy

Email is not a secure means of communication under most circumstances. Never provide sensitive personal information (i.e. Social Security number, driver's license number, or third party credit card information) to us via email. Use the appropriate secured websites to communicate this information or contact our Call Center.

Advance Auto Parts and the Advance Auto Parts family of companies will not sell, trade, share or rent the email address you provide to anyone. We believe that your email address is personal and should be kept that way. We use your email address to provide you with better customer support, and to update you on specials.

## Chat Feature

We use an optional chat feature to assist you with using our Sites. We do not request or collect any personally identifiable information unless it is necessary for assisting you with your specific problem.

## Your Data, Business Transitions

We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties as part of our business operations, however, in the event Advance Auto Parts goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, the personally identifiable information will be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging in to the Site with their username and password, clicking the "Your Account" link found at the top of each page, then clicking the "Your Personal Information" page, and finally clicking the Edit link.

## Protecting Children's Privacy

Our Sites are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13) and so we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13). If we are notified that we have collected personally identifiable information from someone under thirteen (13), we will delete that information promptly upon notification.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site.

## Your Consent

By using our Sites, you (the user) agree to our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions including limitations of damages provisions (as same may apply to you). To the extent that, as a matter of law, Advance Auto Parts may not limit its damages, the scope and duration shall be the minimum permitted under applicable law. Additionally, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Advance Auto Parts and the Advance Auto Parts family of companies as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes to our information practices and will change the date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. If we make changes we will provide notice of such changes on our Sites. If we make material changes, we will provide a more prominent notice of such changes prior to the changes becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients

  * Advance Auto Parts collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

Access and Retention of Data Controlled by our Clients:

  * Advance Auto Parts has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Advance Auto Parts's Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within 30 days.
  * We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Advance Auto Parts will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

This policy was last modified on September 10, 2016.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Advance Auto Parts, Inc.  
5008 Airport Road  
Roanoke, VA 24012
